rezeem.com 2019-09-20

# Rezeem - Privacy Policy

At https://www.rezeem.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit https://www.rezeem.com/ (the “Site”).

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at info@rezeem.com.

**Log Files**

https://www.rezeem.com follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Like any other website, https://www.rezeem.com uses ‘cookies’. These cookies are used to store information including visitors’ preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users’ experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors’ browser type and/or other information.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**

https://www.rezeem.com’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?

**Children’s Information**

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

https://www.rezeem.com does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in https://www.rezeem.com. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Rezeem has the discretion to update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Consent**

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
